More and more sinking
Let's begin the discussion
Oh, here we go.
Yes.
I tried to hold a rock.
She is laughing.
Please go ahead.
I can't take a picture of her.
She is laughing.
I was surprised.
Please go ahead.
I want to meet a comedian.
She is laughing.
I want to produce a person.
I want to do that.
I want to do a common sense test.
I want to know what kind of food I eat.
What?
I don't know.
I saw you eating curry with sauce.
I see.
I want to cook without a recipe.
I can't do that.
It looks fun.
I want to cook a foreign dish.
I don't know.
I want to drive a Mercedes-Benz.
That's good.
I want to drive a Lamborghini or MINI
Cooper.
I want to watch it off.
That's good.
The prank.
If you tell me your plan today,
I will go with you.
That's interesting.
I wonder where you go.
I will go with you.
I want to be a professional wrestler.
That sounds interesting.
I tilt all the cameras this means
Do it pivot
Then I tilt it
I will go to shoot a video of a swing
eating spicy raw beef with from now on.
I want to do it.
I want to play a youth.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Next, they are going to the beach.
They are going to the beach.
I have to be careful not to fall.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Got a lot!?
I'm sweating.
It's a good design.
I'm going to eat a delicious one.
It's amazing.
It's a big one.
I'm going to eat it.
It's really big.
It's big.
It's amazing.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to this channel.
So beautiful!
Wow!
Look at my acting skills!
Wait a minute, stop!
What did you come here to do?
Naturally secret
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is Yasumori Farm!
The reason why I'm here is because I
want to grow my own vegetables!
Wakarin is working hard every day, so I
wanted to grow my own vegetables.
I bought this much.
I'm looking forward to seeing how
Wakarin reacts to this.
I need to color the grass in Yasumori
Farm.
I'm going to use red daikon.
I'm going to do my best as a beginner.
I couldn't make shoes with this
material, so I changed to long shoes.
I'm sorry for borrowing this.
I'm going to cut this.
I want to make Wakarin smile.
I'm always doing my best.
I'm going to water it.
What?
Oh, thank God.
I didn't know that I felt like this.
It's a support for Fujitani.
I didn't know that.
Wow.
Is this OK?
I don't know.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
I'll do my best.
Do you do this every day?
You are good.
I'm scared.
I made a hole.
I'll put 5 grains.
I'm scared.
How can I plant this?
Please subscribe to my channel.
Do you want more?
How much should I put?
It's difficult. I don't know anything.
You can put as much as you like.
Can I put all?
Put as much as you like.
Thank you for watching.
Wow!
Seeds are like this.
I didn't know cosmos is like this.
Thank you for watching my video! Please
subscribe and like!
I'm a person who puts everything in the
bag.
I put everything in the bag.
Because I'm a shrimp type.
This is fun!
Thank you for watching my video!
I wish you grow up a lot!
Is it OK?
Is it OK, Alinko?
Alinko!
I love you!
I'm going to do it.
Oh, no!
What should I do?
I'm going to be found out.
Wait.
I don't want to do it.
If I fall down on the road,
I'm going to be found out.
I don't want to do it.
I'm sad.
I'm going to be found out.
What?
Can you take care of it while I'm gone?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Is this a bird's nest?
It's better to plant it as it is.
I just pulled it out.
Just plant it as it is.
But there are birds coming, so maybe...
Did it drop the seed?
Let's grow it.
Yes.
Wow!
The miracle of the 6th anniversary.
Life has come to life.
Maybe it's a peach seedling.
I'm impressed.
Wow!
It was a peach seedling.
I'm not good at Korean.
Oh, no!
What are you doing?
I put it in the container.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do with the
container.
You can bring a cola that doesn't fit
in the container.
You can do it in front of me.
I want to do it.
I'll change the plan.
Let's go.
OK!
See you next time!
Stop!
Please subscribe to my channel!
That's all.
Good morning.
You just put it in, didn't you?
I did.
I was surprised.
That's all.
That's all for today.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Good job.
I was surprised.
I'm sticky.
Yay!
Today, we are going to eat insects
deliciously.
Who came up with this idea?
Why?
You are right.
I don't know.
We are in E-BEANS.
There is a insect vending machine
behind E-BEANS.
Who is that?
I love E-BEANS, but I can't forgive
this.
Who did you choose?
We bought some insects from there.
I thought you would not like it if we
just ate.
We will think about how to eat insects
deliciously.
There are many ways.
If you like sweet things, you can put
some sweet things on it.
Amatao, it's your turn.
You can do it.
I have been with you for 6 years.
You can eat a lot.
I'm sorry.
You are the worst.
Which do you like, sweet or salty?
I like salty.
You can choose.
Who do you like?
I like sweet.
You are right.
I can't see it.
I'm surprised.
Please hold it.
You are a good person.
My hand slipped.
You are amazing.
You are funny.
I chose.
It contains 28g of protein.
It's amazing.
It's good for trainers.
Insects are nutritious.
Let's eat ice cream.
We're going back.